New York Civil Liberties Union; Records apap331
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- NYCLU Website, 1998 December 5 - 2017 June 3; 1; 715 captures
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 28
    warc_url_count: 52603
    total_data_in_kbs: 3220897
    duplicate_bytes: 2003277277
    warc_compressed_bytes: 495088912
    doc_rate: 0.2
    kb_rate: 12.0
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 28
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 28
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 February 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 March 11
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 March 14
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 March 16
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 March 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 March 28
    crawl: 287154
    start_date: 2017-03-28T19:46:06Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-28T19:46:06Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-31T20:01:30Z
    end_date: 2017-03-31T19:47:29Z
    elapsed_ms: 259250943
    discovered_count: 127328
    novel_count: 30094
    duplicate_count: 22127
    queued_count: 75107
    downloaded_count: 52221
    warc_revisit_count: 22097
    warc_url_count: 52202
    total_data_in_kbs: 4462980
    duplicate_bytes: 2802673643
    warc_compressed_bytes: 875185848
    kb_rate: 17.0
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 March 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 April 12
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 April 21
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 April 28
    crawl: 297803
    start_date: 2017-04-28T19:45:56Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-28T19:45:56Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-01T20:10:48Z
    end_date: 2017-05-01T19:49:05Z
    elapsed_ms: 259369267
    discovered_count: 135997
    novel_count: 37274
    duplicate_count: 23891
    queued_count: 74832
    downloaded_count: 61165
    warc_revisit_count: 23872
    warc_url_count: 61145
    total_data_in_kbs: 4626461
    duplicate_bytes: 2183654141
    warc_compressed_bytes: 470097078
    doc_rate: 0.24
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 April 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 May 13
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 May 19
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 May 20
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 May 25
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 May 28
    crawl: 303738
    start_date: 2017-05-28T19:45:50Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-28T19:45:50Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-31T20:07:05Z
    end_date: 2017-05-31T19:47:49Z
    elapsed_ms: 259302658
    discovered_count: 124052
    novel_count: 28649
    duplicate_count: 20723
    queued_count: 74680
    downloaded_count: 49372
    warc_revisit_count: 20690
    warc_url_count: 49355
    total_data_in_kbs: 3483081
    duplicate_bytes: 2264201448
    warc_compressed_bytes: 417920994
    doc_rate: 0.19
    kb_rate: 13.0
  - WARC file for New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 May 28
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 2017 June 3
- Legal Case Files, 1951-1995; 2; 500 cubic ft.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Certain Restrictions May Apply.
  The legal case files series spans from freedom of speech, religion, press, petition, and assembly, to privacy, to equality before and due process of law. The legal cases show the expansive service the NYCLU performs for underrepresented groups and person of New York State.
  Arrangement
  Arranged Alphabetically.
- Executive Director, 1951-1995; 3
  The Executive Director files contain the material of past Executive Directors, the NYCLU Board, including board meeting minutes, and chapter news.
  Arranged Chronologically.
- Legislative Committee, 1951-1995; 4
  The legislative Committee series tracks the work of the NYCLU and their impact advocating for New Yorkers through reform. In 1970, a campaign led by the NYCLU's legislative office lead to the repeal of a state law that imposes criminal sanctions for the performance of medical abortions.
- Advocacy, 1951-1995; 5
- Subject Files, 1951-1995; 6